// This is the data for the quiz questions, answers, and choices
var quizData = [
  {
    "question": "Database used by the entire organization",
    "answer": "Enterprise database",
    "choices": [
      "Enterprise database",
      "Centralized database",
      "Cloud database",
      "General-purpose database"
    ],
    "reference": "01 Activity 1 - ARG",
    "term": "Prelim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Database that supports data located at a single site",
    "answer": "Centralized database",
    "choices": [
      "Centralized database",
      "Enterprise database",
      "Cloud database",
      "General-purpose database"
    ],
    "reference": "01 Activity 1 - ARG",
    "term": "Prelim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Microsoft Azure and AWS are examples of this database type.",
    "answer": "Cloud database",
    "choices": [
      "Cloud database",
      "Centralized database",
      "Enterprise database",
      "General-purpose database"
    ],
    "reference": "01 Activity 1 - ARG",
    "term": "Prelim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Data is unaffected by changes.",
    "answer": "Data independence",
    "choices": [
      "Data independence",
      "Data inconsistency",
      "Structural dependence",
      "Data dependence"
    ],
    "reference": "01 Activity 1 - ARG",
    "term": "Prelim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Conflicting versions for the same data appear in different places.",
    "answer": "Data inconsistency",
    "choices": [
      "Data inconsistency",
      "Data independence",
      "Structural dependence",
      "Data dependence"
    ],
    "reference": "01 Activity 1 - ARG",
    "term": "Prelim"
  },
  {
    "question": "A change in a database schema requires changes in other programs.",
    "answer": "Structural dependence",
    "choices": [
      "Structural dependence",
      "Data inconsistency",
      "Data independence",
      "Structural Independence"
    ],
    "reference": "01 Activity 1 - ARG",
    "term": "Prelim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Database that contains a wide variety of data",
    "answer": "General-purpose database",
    "choices": [
      "General-purpose database",
      "Centralized database",
      "Enterprise database",
      "Cloud database"
    ],
    "reference": "01 Activity 1 - ARG",
    "term": "Prelim"
  },
  {
    "question": "A change in a database schema does not affect other programs.",
    "answer": "Structural independence",
    "choices": [
      "Structural independence",
      "Structural dependence",
      "Data inconsistency",
      "Data independence"
    ],
    "reference": "01 Activity 1 - ARG",
    "term": "Prelim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Database used for strategic decision making",
    "answer": "Analytical database",
    "choices": [
      "Analytical database",
      "Enterprise database",
      "Centralized database",
      "Cloud database"
    ],
    "reference": "01 Activity 1 - ARG",
    "term": "Prelim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Database that contains data which are focused on particular subject areas",
    "answer": "Discipline-specific database",
    "choices": [
      "Discipline-specific database",
      "Enterprise database",
      "Cloud database",
      "General-purpose database"
    ],
    "reference": "01 Activity 1 - ARG",
    "term": "Prelim"
  }
]